<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hecrer</title>
    <link>https://hecrer.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hecrer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 17:04:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hecrer.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Charles Leclerc</title>
      <link>https://hecrer.github.io/posts/leclerc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 17:04:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hecrer.github.io/posts/leclerc/</guid>
      <description>&#34;For Tonio.&#34; Charles Leclerc took his first win in 2019 at Spa, in the wake of the heartbreaking loss of Anthoine Hubert in a crash earlier that weekend, and dedicated his victory to his late friend. I felt this moment, originally captured by a Ferrari hired photographer, captured the intense emotions that Leclerc must have been feeling as he climbed out of his Ferrari after the race.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chasing Cars (Cover) - Snow Patrol</title>
      <link>https://hecrer.github.io/posts/chasing_cars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 17:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hecrer.github.io/posts/chasing_cars/</guid>
      <description>Your browser does not support the audio element. 
A much more low effort cover than my previous (expect more of this - I&amp;rsquo;m lazy). Sometimes it&amp;rsquo;s nice to just grab a guitar and try a rendition of a song you haven&amp;rsquo;t heard in years, Chasing Cars came out whilst I was in my early teens and I remember it doing the rounds at school on the twenty(ish) songs worth of storage mp3 players at the time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://hecrer.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hecrer.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi there!
I go by Hecrer and I usually work as a Software Engineer, but this site is a place for my music and doodles and maybe a few other things too. I hope you have a good time here!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapel Song (Cover) - Augustines</title>
      <link>https://hecrer.github.io/posts/chapel_song/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2019 13:28:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hecrer.github.io/posts/chapel_song/</guid>
      <description>Your browser does not support the audio element. 
My take on Chapel Song, the first track on the album Rise Ye Sunken Ships by Augustines. I first saw this song on a live Cardinal Session on YouTube, and it&amp;rsquo;s been one of my favourite songs to play since.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Valtteri Bottas</title>
      <link>https://hecrer.github.io/posts/bottas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 18:47:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hecrer.github.io/posts/bottas/</guid>
      <description>&#34;Valtteri, it&#39;s James.&#34; I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on some art for a new project that expands the service our Server Manager provides for Assetto Corsa. Here&amp;rsquo;s Bottas.
This was my first time using an iPad (the iPad Pro 2018, that I borrowed) to draw something, and i&amp;rsquo;m pretty happy with how it came out! Mixing the &amp;ldquo;real&amp;rdquo; feeling of using a traditional pencil directly onto a drawing surface with all of the added benefits that come with working in art software really does create a powerful and unique experience.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>