<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Hecrer</title>
    <link>https://hecrer.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Hecrer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 18:55:21 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hecrer.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I Will Follow You Into the Dark (Cover) - Death Cab For Cutie</title>
      <link>https://hecrer.github.io/posts/i-will-follow-you-into-the-dark/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 18:55:21 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hecrer.github.io/posts/i-will-follow-you-into-the-dark/</guid>
      <description>Your browser does not support the audio element. 
Death is a difficult topic to approach, and many artists have their own take on dealing with the loss of their loved ones. This song resonated with me a lot when I first heard it some ten years ago, and it&amp;rsquo;s one I revisit every so often. It&amp;rsquo;s also probably one of the most covered tracks by Death Cab For Cutie, and here I am adding to the list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wicked Game (Cover) - Chris Isaak(/Stone Sour)</title>
      <link>https://hecrer.github.io/posts/wicked_game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2020 16:24:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hecrer.github.io/posts/wicked_game/</guid>
      <description>Your browser does not support the audio element. 
I seem to be making a habit of covering covers! This is one of the first songs I ever learnt, and listening to this recent recording of it really shows me how much I&amp;rsquo;ve improved over the years, hopefully that trend continues! Sometimes it&amp;rsquo;s nice to look back, and this song is one of my less embarrassing favourites from my angst phase.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Someone Like You (Cover) - Adele(/Smith and Myers)</title>
      <link>https://hecrer.github.io/posts/someone_like_you/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 16:26:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hecrer.github.io/posts/someone_like_you/</guid>
      <description>Your browser does not support the audio element. 
This is a cover of a cover, Smith and Myers (of Shinedown) played a rendition of Someone Like You for their acoustic EP. It sounds like a new Smith and Myers EP will be coming out soon, spurring me to have a go at this song.
Shinedown were a huge part of my early adventures into music, being one of the first bands I listened to that I hadn&amp;rsquo;t heard through my parents first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Laws of Love and War (Cover) - The Glorious Sons</title>
      <link>https://hecrer.github.io/posts/the_laws_of_love_and_war/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 17:29:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hecrer.github.io/posts/the_laws_of_love_and_war/</guid>
      <description>Your browser does not support the audio element. 
More Glorious Sons! The guitar part for this song is a bit more technical than anything I&amp;rsquo;ve uploaded so far, I think I did an okay job of it! I can&amp;rsquo;t stop playing songs by this band, I think the writing generally suits a one-man cover and they&amp;rsquo;re great fun to learn. I&amp;rsquo;ll make sure my next cover is of a different band though.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A War On Everything (Cover) - The Glorious Sons</title>
      <link>https://hecrer.github.io/posts/a_war_on_everything/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 19:38:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hecrer.github.io/posts/a_war_on_everything/</guid>
      <description>Your browser does not support the audio element. 
The Glorious Sons are a rock band from Canada, and they were the main soundtrack to the first roadtrip me and some friends took around central Europe. After that we were lucky enough to catch them at a (free!) gig in London, which cemented my love for the band as they swung from the rafters and belted out tune after tune, the energy and heart of their performance makes it easy to feel a connection to the band live and get lost in the moment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charles Leclerc</title>
      <link>https://hecrer.github.io/posts/leclerc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 17:04:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hecrer.github.io/posts/leclerc/</guid>
      <description>&#34;For Tonio.&#34; Charles Leclerc took his first win in 2019 at Spa, in the wake of the heartbreaking loss of Anthoine Hubert in a crash earlier that weekend, and dedicated his victory to his late friend. I felt this moment, originally captured by a Ferrari hired photographer, captured the intense emotions that Leclerc must have been feeling as he climbed out of his Ferrari after the race.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chasing Cars (Cover) - Snow Patrol</title>
      <link>https://hecrer.github.io/posts/chasing_cars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 17:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hecrer.github.io/posts/chasing_cars/</guid>
      <description>Your browser does not support the audio element. 
A much more low effort cover than my previous (expect more of this - I&amp;rsquo;m lazy). Sometimes it&amp;rsquo;s nice to just grab a guitar and try a rendition of a song you haven&amp;rsquo;t heard in years, Chasing Cars came out whilst I was in my early teens and I remember it doing the rounds at school on the twenty(ish) songs worth of storage mp3 players at the time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapel Song (Cover) - Augustines</title>
      <link>https://hecrer.github.io/posts/chapel_song/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2019 13:28:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hecrer.github.io/posts/chapel_song/</guid>
      <description>Your browser does not support the audio element. 
My take on Chapel Song, the first track on the album Rise Ye Sunken Ships by Augustines. I first saw this song on a live Cardinal Session on YouTube, and it&amp;rsquo;s been one of my favourite songs to play since.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Valtteri Bottas</title>
      <link>https://hecrer.github.io/posts/bottas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 18:47:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hecrer.github.io/posts/bottas/</guid>
      <description>&#34;Valtteri, it&#39;s James.&#34; I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on some art for a new project that expands the service our Server Manager provides for Assetto Corsa. Here&amp;rsquo;s Bottas.
This was my first time using an iPad (the iPad Pro 2018, that I borrowed) to draw something, and i&amp;rsquo;m pretty happy with how it came out! Mixing the &amp;ldquo;real&amp;rdquo; feeling of using a traditional pencil directly onto a drawing surface with all of the added benefits that come with working in art software really does create a powerful and unique experience.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>